Xiao Yi
肖毅
This is the woman who lives next door to him
这是住在他隔壁的女人
suspects
嫌疑人
from now on
今后
in this case
在这种情况下
The woman who lives next door to him
住在他隔壁的女人
perhaps
大概
we have been looking for
我们一直在寻找
This is Mr. Zhang
这是张先生
Xiao Yi's photos
肖毅的照片
we got it
我们得到了它
But be careful with this woman
但要小心这个女人
very high
很高
We went to their neighborhood
我们去了他们的邻居
But the surveillance camera was found
但发现监控摄像头
they were cheated
他们被骗了
So we didn't find
所以我们没有找到
any direct photos
任何直接的照片
Where is the inspection team?
检查组在哪里？
they entered her house
他们进入了她的房子
Verify
核实
I hope in the future
我希望在未来
Find other evidence
寻找其他证据
under any circumstances
任何状况之下
Master Zhang finally appeared
张师傅终于出现了
How is Chu Yan?
楚炎怎么样了？
Yes
是的
She knows it's limited
她知道这是有限的
you didn't go
你没有去
In Xiao Yi’s life
在肖毅的生活中
Let me see the interrogation video
让我看一下审讯视频
except name
除了名字
do you know
你知道吗
Other information about him
关于他的其他信息
For example
例如
another phone number
另一个电话号码
family address
家庭地址
or
或者
Do you have any friends in common?
你们有共同的朋友吗？
No
不
these glasses
这些眼镜
When did you buy it?
你什么时候买的？
This is from Xiaoyi
这是小毅发来的
when
什么时候
a week ago
一个星期前
I was very busy
我当时很忙
Ignore him for now
暂时不理他
but he remembers
但他记得
our memory
我们的回忆
All right
好吧
What crime did he commit?
他犯了什么罪？
Don't worry about him now
现在不用担心他
but you
但是你
did you see?
你有没有看到？
You are doing it for him now
你现在是为了他
you have not
你没有
no usable value
没有可利用价值
Is everything fake?
一切都是假的吗？
Maybe even his name
甚至可能是他的名字
Forged
伪造的
But you helped him
但你帮了他
Steal state secrets
窃取国家机密
this is correct
这是对的
on the way back
回去的路上
What did he tell you?
他告诉你什么了？
He said he would take me to see the sunrise
他说要带我去看日出
sunrise
日出
Yes
是的
Because I'm always dreaming
因为我总是在做梦
Want to own a villa by the sea
想要拥有一栋临海的别墅
I can watch the sunrise
我可以看日出
Go watch the sunrise and sunset
去看日出和日落
Can you wear these glasses?
你能戴上这副眼镜吗？
one
一
beach villa
海滩别墅
Do you think Xiao Yi will accept it?
你觉得萧毅会接受吗？
before saying this
在说这句话之前
He didn't know he had been exposed
他并不知道自己已经暴露了
but he
但是他
Do whatever it takes to please
想尽一切办法取悦
Chu Yan’s wish
楚炎的愿望
Tianyang, what do you think?
天阳，你觉得怎么样？
Given their event rules
鉴于他们的活动规则
He won't buy a villa
他不会买别墅
But it can be rented
但可以租
let us check
让我们检查
OK
好的
I'll ask the technical department
我去问一下技术部
Verify
核实
Xiaoyi’s consumption record
小易的消费记录
Probably
很可能是
a hiding place
一个藏身之处
welcome
欢迎
The number you dialed is out of service
您拨打的号码已停机
I found Xiao Yi’s residence
我找到了肖毅的住处
three days ago
三天前
Sea view villa for rent
出租观海别墅
a month
一个月
Have you informed Director Chen?
你通知陈主任了​​吗？
Yes
是的
Other groups have taken off
其他团体已起飞
Go to website
前往网站
Okay, I'll go right away
好的，我马上就去
are you looking for me?
你在找我吗？
waiting for me
正在等我
I let go
我放水
Shall we go together?
我们一起去吗？
I take a gun with me in the shower
我洗澡时带着枪
And you can't take a shower with a gun
而且你不能拿着枪洗澡
kill me
杀了我
impossible
不可能
mission accomplished
完成任务
I'll brush my teeth first
我先刷牙
Didn’t we agree to clean up first?
我们不是说好的先清理吗？
The same to you
你也是
Have you gained weight recently?
你最近变胖了吗？
you must kill him
你必须杀了他
you know a lot
你知道很多
besides it
此外它
.Full Revealed
.完全揭晓
They are afraid that you will not be able to escape from Tianhai.
他们怕你逃不出天海。
if i say
如果我说
I can find a way to go
我能找到一条路走
I can't kill you
我杀不了你
I didn't complete the task
我没有完成任务
I'm not here to kill you
我不是来杀你的
You betrayed the organization
你背叛了组织
you know i have no choice
你知道我别无选择
now my work is done
现在我的工作完成了
I can't kill you
我杀不了你
you have completed your task
你已经完成了你的任务
Your skink is poisonous
你的石龙子有毒
follow me
跟我来
are you happy?
你快乐吗？
I'm your partner
我是你的伙伴
very good
非常好
Xiao Yi was poisoned
小易中毒了
Quickly
迅速地
Call an ambulance quickly
赶紧叫救护车
science
科学
Come on, be careful
来吧，小心一点
come over
过来
Sorry, you can't enter
抱歉，您无法进入
He went to the emergency room
他进了急诊室
Has it been processed?
已经处理了吗？
Yes
是的
But Guoan came quickly
但国安来得很快
no time to be sure
没有时间确定
this matter
这件事
cannot have any errors
不能有任何错误
you killed him
你杀了他
if he is still alive
如果他还活着
Will he help us?
他会帮助我们吗？
To keep a secret?
为了保守秘密？
Is he alive or dead?
他是活着还是死了？
Give me an explanation
给我一个解释
Understood
明白了
Sister, you're late
姐姐，来晚了
Good morning, President
早上好，总统
Good morning, Sir
早上好先生
Sister, I'm done
姐姐我说完了
Are you OK
你好吗
I am fine
我很好
Go to work
去工作
OK
好的
How is the patient?
病人怎么样？
Although temporarily saved
虽然暂时得救了
but his signs of life
但他的生命迹象
unstable
不稳定
at any time
随时
72 hours later
72小时后
Very important
很重要
We have to continue to monitor
我们还得继续监测
How long will it take
它需要多长时间
Handshake
握手
if he could
如果他可以的话
he can succeed
他能成功
I think it's very likely
我认为可能性很大
he will get up early
他会早起
he told the police
他告诉警察
It turns out that this villa
原来这栋别墅
Because it is rented out
因为对外出租
there are many people there
那里有很多人
Therefore, it is very difficult to investigate
所以调查起来难度很大
As for the examination group
至于考试组
Only in this villa
只在这栋别墅里
in this villa
在这栋别墅里
about 37
约37
Judging from female footprints
从女性的脚印来看
It's for Mr. Zhang
是给张先生的
do something
做某事
Help yourself
帮助自己
The inspection team found
检查组发现
Other fingerprints are incomplete
其他指纹不完整
not long ago
不久之前
when i enter the villa
当我进入别墅时
Judging from the clarity of this fingerprint
从这个指纹的清晰程度来看
we can judge
我们可以判断
he recently left her
他最近离开了她
Only half a piece
只有半块
But honestly
但老实说
This fingerprint
这个指纹
doesn't make much sense to us
对我们来说没有多大意义
we don't know at all
我们根本不知道
Where is the owner of the fingerprint?
指纹的主人在哪里？
Do you have any opinion
你有什么意见
OK
好的
eat
吃
my sisters
我的姐妹
I gotta go
我要走了
See you tomorrow
明天见
sorry i came too late
抱歉，我来得太晚了
I see you're activating night flight mode
我看到你正在启动夜间飞行模式
I know you are busy again
我知道你又忙了
Yes
是的
Cook a pot of pasta
煮一锅意大利面
OK
好的
I want to drink some wine
我想喝点酒
a cup of beer
一杯啤酒
Pasta with beer
意大利面配啤酒
Fashion
时尚
Would you like a drink too?
你也想喝一杯吗？
OK
好的
comfortable
舒服的
can you help me
你可以帮帮我吗
Some dishes with wine
一些放酒的菜
no problem
没问题
Thanks
谢谢
eat slowly
慢慢吃
I'm hungry
我饿了
let's go
我们走吧
Thanks
谢谢
Are you OK
你好吗
Can't compare
无法比较
We only have half of our fingerprints
我们只有一半的指纹
your mark
你的印记
Fingerprints are not clear
指纹不清晰
unconfirmed
无法确定
The boundaries have been blurred
界限已经模糊
look
看
these places
这些地方
Remove skin from fingers
去除手指上的皮肤
Will it cause fingerprint haze?
会不会导致指纹雾霾
Yes
是的
Xiao Yi is still alive
萧毅还活着
He may wake up at any time
他随时可能醒来
How are you going to deal with Huang Ziqing?
你准备怎么对付黄子晴？
Since Huang Ziqing
自从黄自清
He is Gao Tianyang's informant
他是高天阳的线人
for us
为了我们
worthless
毫无价值的
He will not return to Tianhai alive
他不会活着回到天海
Huang Zicheng was killed
黄子成被杀
means nothing to you
对你来说没有任何意义
Of course it has its meaning
当然有它的意义
He will make these
他会让这些
who wants to deceive us
谁想欺骗我们
Don't you dare lie anymore?
你不敢再撒谎吗
if you want to kill him
如果你想杀他
No need to wait long
无需等待很长时间
Still very useful
还是很有用的
yaw yaw
偏航 偏航
You are becoming more and more like me
你越来越像我了
experienced spy
经验丰富的间谍
No wonder Mr. Yu
难怪于先生
I don't want to abandon you
我不想抛弃你
Huang Ziqing is definitely helpful
黄子晴绝对有帮助
But this mission
但这个使命
you need to finish it
你需要完成它
What is the mission?
使命是什么？
Search for "Gao Tianyang".
搜索“高天阳”。
Looking for Gao Tianyang
寻找高天阳
open the door
打开门
let's eat
我们吃饭吧
go out to eat
出去吃
my sisters
我的姐妹
Can I come up for air?
我可以上来呼吸空气吗？
No
不
allow
允许
Okay, okay, can I go?
好吧好吧我可以走了吗？
go see tony
去见托尼
No
不
my sister my sister
我的妹妹，我的妹妹
no problem, no problem
没关系，没关系
Eat food
吃食物
presentable
体面的
we need to
我们需要
Better than Huang Zicheng
比黄子成强
You want to exploit Huang Ziqing?
你想剥削黄子晴
To bring out the sunset
为了衬托出夕阳
It's Gao Tianyang
是高天阳
in our plan
在我们的计划中
But we must start early
但我们必须尽早开始
But this is from Duane
但这是来自杜安的
He wants to pull it out
他想把它拔出来
What will happen?
会怎么样呢？
it depends
这取决于
for him
为了他
everything
一切
You need to analyze the pros and cons
你需要分析好处和坏处
It’s just that the chip doesn’t fit
只是芯片不适合
No transaction is possible
没有交易是不可能的
Why do you want me to leave?
你为什么要我走？
If Gao Tianyang disagrees
如果高天阳不同意
I will fall into a trap
我会掉进陷阱
You are Huang Ziqing’s partner
你是黄子晴的搭档
I've met Gao Tianyang before
我以前见过高天阳
No one is more suitable for you
没有人更适合你
Can Huang Zicheng come back alive?
黄子成是否还能活着回来
depends on you
取决于你
Do you think
你认为
Can I deal with Gao Tianyang?
我能对付高天阳吗？
No need to pay attention to him
没必要搭理他
Just let him know
只要让他知道
it's dangerous
这很危险
As for other arrangements
至于其他安排
I will tell you
我会告诉你
we will understand the situation
我们会了解情况
and are always available to help you
并随时为您提供帮助
Hello
你好
My brother Tianyang
我的天阳哥哥
This is me Yaoyao
这就是我瑶瑶
What happened to Huang Ziqing?
黄子晴怎么了？
Take him out of the night fog
带他走出夜雾
Where is he now?
他现在在哪儿？
in the same boat
在同一条船里
Why did they arrest him?
他们为什么逮捕他？
Because Huang Zicheng is your informant
因为黄子成是你的线人
Who said that?
谁说的？
He said so himself
他自己也这么说
Huang Ziqing and I
我和黄子晴
I'm the pawn in your quarrel
是你们吵架的棋子
listen carefully
仔细听
you can sit here now
你现在可以坐在这里
she talks to me
她跟我说话
I hid
我藏起来了
For you
为你
Otherwise you will arrest him
否则你会逮捕他
this is my man
这是我的男人
To present you with results
为了向您呈现成果
Did you cheat on him?
你欺骗他了吗？
I'm asking you
我在问你
How did they know?
他们怎么知道的？
find out
查出
The documents Huang Ziqing took were fake
黄子晴拿走的文件是假的
He forced me to investigate him
他强迫我调查他
I know
我知道
sorry
对不起
I have no expectations
我没有期待
it's important
这很重要
therefore
因此
I didn't expect anything
我没想到什么
at the beginning
在一开始的时候
you play games together
你们一起玩游戏
Why don't you think about it?
你为什么不想想？
What's the end of today?
今天的结局是什么？
but me too
但我也是
force me
强迫我
to this limit
到这个限度
Do you think you are innocent?
你认为你是无辜的吗？
I'm not innocent
我并不无辜
i know i did it
我知道我做到了
many errors
很多错误
He doesn't deserve to forgive me
他不值得原谅我
but i still want to
但我还是想
To Huang Zicheng
致黄子成
to find you
去寻找你
i want to tell you
我想告诉你
everything
一切
you can
你可以
at any time
随时
But my brother Tianyang
但我的天阳哥哥
please
请
Please save Huang Ziqing
请救救黄子晴
Because you are the only one now
因为现在只有你一个人
to save him
为了救他
What are their conditions?
他们的条件是什么？
Tony said
托尼说
He wants to see you alone
他想单独见你
you can go alone
你可以一个人去
Where?
在哪里？
Mr. Gao Tianyang
高天阳先生
welcome
欢迎
Don't you want to meet and talk?
难道你不想见面谈谈吗？
This is also an interview
这也是采访
in this era
在这个时代
distance is not a problem
距离不是问题
Where is Huang Zicheng?
黄子成在哪里？
He's here
他在这里
let me see
让我看看
we haven't talked yet
我们还没聊过
before we talk
在我们谈话之前
Not very good
不是很好
hurry up
快点
Huang Ziqing was released
黄子晴被释放
what is it
它是什么
Get rid of Xiao Yi
摆脱萧毅
Do you think it's possible?
您认为可能吗？
She wants me to kill someone
她要我杀人
Persons protected by the National Security Agency
受国家安全局保护的人
i don't care what i do
我不在乎我做什么
we just want results
我们只想要结果
i can't do this
我不能这样做
presentable
体面的
I'll give you some time to think
我会给你一些时间思考
Xiao Yi and Huang Zicheng
肖毅和黄子成
Who is most important?
谁最重要？
Did you cheat on him?
你欺骗他了吗？
but I do not have
但我没有
i'm using you
我在利用你
i always want to
我一直想
Be your scapegoat
成为你的替罪羊
and take you to the beach
并带你去海滩
Have you met Gao Tianyang?
你见过高天阳吗？
I went out in the afternoon
我下午出去了
Mr. Gao
高先生
Isn't this appropriate?
这不合适吗？
Is this impolite?
这是不礼貌的吗？
I have to keep him safe
我必须确保他的安全
we can
我们可以
Let’s talk next time
我们下次再聊吧
his safety
他的安全
You need to alternate actions
你需要交替进行动作
your terms
您的条款
very difficult for me
对我来说非常困难
i need more time
我需要更多的时间
Decide
决定
During this period
在此期间
I hope Huang Ziqing is safe
希望黄子晴平安
sorry
对不起
this is not
这不是
equality
平等对待
you don't have much time
你没有太多时间
Let's play an old game
我们来玩一个老游戏吧
Russian wheel
俄罗斯轮
Do you dare to come?
你敢来吗？
If I say I can't play
如果我说我不会玩
you have to find a way
你必须想办法
force me
强迫我